I hate the word "fate."
僕は運命って言葉が嫌いだ
Birth, encounters, partings,
生まれ　出会い　別れ
success and failure,
成功と失敗
fortune and misfortune in life.
人生の幸　不幸
If everything is already set in stone by fate,
それらが予め運命によって 決められているのなら
then why are we even born?
僕達は何のために生まれてくるんだろう
There are those born wealthy,
裕福な家庭に生まれる人
those born of beautiful mothers,
美しい母親から生まれる人
and those born into war or poverty.
飢餓や戦争の真っ只中に生まれる人
If that's all caused by fate, then God must be incredibly unfair and cruel.
それらが全て運命だとすれば
神様って奴はとんでもなく理不尽で残酷だ
あの時から僕達には未来なんてなく
Because, ever since that day, none of us had a future.
The only thing we knew was that we would never amount to anything.
ただ　きっと何者にも成れないって事だけがはっきりしてたんだから
くるくる回る
<< kurukuru mawaru kimi no hitomi >>
<< Round and round, your eyes wander around >>
君の瞳探して回る
<< sagashite mawaru eki no home >>
<< Searching around the station's platforms >>
駅のホーム
<< hibiku fanfare >>
<< The sound of fanfare from afar >>
響くファンファーレ
ガラガラ音を立てる街
<< garagara oto wo tateru machi >>
<< The clamorous city making noise >>
<< toriaezu mimi wo kashite ita no >>
<< I tried to keep an ear out for all this >>
とりあえず耳を貸してみたの
<< mousugu kieru hazu no sekai ni >>
<< In a world that's about to end >>
もうすぐ　消えるはずの世界に
御免ね
<< gomen ne >>
<< I'm sorry >>
もう二度と会えないようなそんな気がして
<< mou nido to aenai youna sonna ki ga shite >>
<< I just had a feeling I would never see you again >>
運命が笑う
<< unmei ga warau >>
<< Fate is laughing at us >>
臨界点突破してんだ
<< rinkaiten toppa shiten da >>
<< I'm already past the point of no return >>
限界なら既に去って
<< genkai nara sude ni satte >>
<< Far over my limit >>
絶対的支配だって
<< zettaiteki shihai datte >>
<< Even your absolute control has >>
崩壊
<< houkai >>
<< Crumbled >>
終末理論は机上の空論でしかないって
<< shuumatsu riron wa kijou no kuuron shika naitte >>
<< "The end of the world is nothing but a hypothesis" >>
ゼロとイチの世界線の果てから
<< 0 to 1 no sekaisen no hate kara sakebu yo >>
<< Is what I'm crying out from other side of the binary world line >>
叫ぶよ
もうすぐ君が会いにくるような気がして
<< mou sugu kimi ga ai ni kuru you na ki ga shite >>
<< I have a feeling you'll come see me soon >>
僕は目を閉じるよ
<< boku wa me wo tojiru yo >>
<< So I will be waiting with my eyes closed >>
本字幕由诸神字幕组(www.kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
时间轴：wcaster  压制：wcaster
日听 xHunter 翻译：小音 校对：要命的小宇、木落
Isn't it electrifying?
痺れるだろう
諦めないで　まだ世界は終ったわけじゃないか
Don't give up just yet.
The world hasn't stopped turning yet.
Who are you?
あんた　何者だ
I'll keep my introduction brief.
自己紹介は手短に
I was transferred to this hospital today.
本日付で　当病院に着任したんだ
It's a pleasure to meet you.
どうぞ　よろしく
What's that?
それは
It's a gift I brought for you, from somewhere far away.
これは　遠い所から運んで来た
君達への　お土産
Shall we initiate the Survival Strategy?
生存戦略　しましょうか
What... did you just say?
今　何って
さて
Well then.
目下なところ　君はとても無力で惨めな子供だ
As far as I can tell, you're quite a helpless and pitiful child.
大切な妹すら助けられずに
Powerless to even save your precious little sister,
able only to loathe your own fate.
ただ己の運命を恨むのみ
But I have the power to...
だが　僕なら
その薬は
What's that medicine?
お姫様の眠りを覚ます
You might call it the prince's kiss to wake sleeping beauty.
王子様のキスってところかな
罰なんだ
It's our punishment.
もし　このままひまりが目を覚まさなかったら
If Himari never wakes up again, it's a punishment bestowed upon our family.
それは僕達家族に下された罰なんだ
だって　そうだろう
It has to be.
父さんと母さんがした事を考えたら
Considering what my parents have done...
僕らはどんなことをしたって償い切れない
There's nothing we can do to atone for their crimes.
But...
そんな
分かってたんだ　ホントは
To be honest, I knew...
that this day would come eventually.
いつか こんな日が来るって
Shoma - Three Years Ago - Takakura Home, Night - Takakura family's crime and punishment. Part 1: That day, our ordinary life was stripped from us.
そうさ
That's right, ever since that day three years ago.
三年前のあの日から
Mom and Dad sure are late.
遅いなー　父さんと母さん
Are they working overtime or something?
残業でもしてるのかな
もう先に食っちゃうぜ
Let's just eat without them!
駄目だよ
No!
御飯は家族みんなでが家の家訓だろう
"Dinner is family time," is our family motto.
That's stupid!
阿呆くそ
やっぱりお母さんの味噌汁は宇宙一だね
Mom's miso soup is definitely the best in the universe!
Geez, Himari!
って　ひまり
Coming!
はい
はい　今開けまー
Yes, I'm coming-
君は高倉晶馬君の方だね
You are Takakura... Shouma, correct?
おい　どうした
Hey, what's up?
そっちの君が冠葉君か
You must be Kanba.
妹のひまりさんも奥にいるのかな
Is your little sister, Himari, back there too?
Hold on, who are you people?
おい　ちょっと　何だよ　あんたら
お父さんとお母さんはお留守よね
Your Mommy and Daddy aren't home, right?
Did they contact you, by any chance?
何か連絡はあったかな
何の用か　知らねえけど
I don't know what you want from us, but don't just waltz in-
勝手に人の家に
Kan!
冠ちゃん
Stay in your room!
お前は部屋にいろ
電話　池部のおじさんから
Phone call... from Uncle Ikebe.
大事な話だって
He says it's important.
はい　俺です　冠葉
Yes. It's me.
Kanba.
今　玄関に変な奴らが来てて
A bunch of weird guys are at the door.
その人達は警察だ
They are the police.
いいか
Listen to me carefully.
数日分の着替えを持って　一緒に家を出ろ
Leave the house with a couple day's worth of clothes.
晶馬もひまりも一緒にだ
Take Shoma and Himari with you.
何も聞くな　俺もすぐにお前達のところへ行くから
Just do it.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
詳しい事はその時に話す
I'll explain everything later.
何もかもあんまり急で
Everything happened so suddenly.
何かが可笑しいって気づく暇もなかった
I didn't even have the time to realize something was wrong.
本当にいつもと同じ一日だったんだ
It really was a day like as any other.
朝　みんなで御飯を食べて
We had breakfast together in the morning.
僕達は学校
The three of us went to school.
父さんと母さんは仕事
Our parents went to work.
玄関で笑って　手を振って
We smiled by the door and waved.
でも　それっきり二人は帰って来なかった
But they never came back.
それが最後　僕達が普通の家族でいられた日
That was the last time we were together as a family.
僕達が普通の子供でいられた日は　終わった
Our days as normal children had ended.
あれから　幾度目覚めても
We've been waking up to a different world ever since.
僕らにあの日と同じ朝は来ない
永遠に
Never the same again.
で　どうする
So, what will you do?
あいにく　このお土産は安くないんだ
Unfortunately, this gift comes at a steep price.
After all, it's a valuable new medicine.
何しろ　貴重な新薬だからね
There are countless patients waiting to get their hands on it.
世界中でこの薬を待ち望む患者はごまんといる
You want money?
金か
If that is what you feel is a suitable exchange for sister's life.
妹の命の代価として　君がそれを相応しいと思うなら
I'll pay, so hurry and-
金なら払う
だから　速く
It's not a sum that a parentless high school student could afford.
親のいない高校生に払える金額じゃないよ
I know where to get the money.
当てはある　約束する
I swear.
Oh?
これを担保にしてかい
With this as a collateral?
なんのことだ
What are you talking about?
そうまでする価値　彼女にあるの
Is she worth doing all that for?
大切な妹だ
She's my precious little sister.
その報酬として　君が得るものは
What's in it for you?
妹のために　百遍その身を焼いて
What will be left after burning it away a hundred times for her sake?
それで君に何が残る
黒焦げになった醜いサソリの心臓
The hideous, charred heart of a Scorpion?
Or stark, white ash?
それとも　真っ白な灰
I don't want anything for myself!
俺は何も欲しくない
I wouldn't even dream of it!
欲しいとも思わない
ただ　ひまりさえいれば
As long as Himari is with me...
早くしろ　あんた医者だろ
Hurry up... aren't you a doctor?
痺れるね
That's electrifying.
契約成立
We have a deal!
さすがです　眞悧先生
Impressive, Dr. Sanetoshi!
だよね
I know, right?
じゃ　そういう事で
Well then, that settles it.
Shoma - Three Years Ago - Shinjuku Kaioh Plaza Hotel - Takakura family's crime and punishment. Part 2: That day, our love was stripped from us.
What do you mean by "stay here for a while"?
暫くここにいろって　どういう事だよ
What happened to our home?
家に何があったんだ
家に電話させてください
Please let us call home.
父さんたちが帰って来て　僕らが居なかったら心配すると思うんです
Our parents will be worried if we're not there when they get back.
御免なさい　我慢してくれるかな
I'm sorry, will you put up with it for us?
I can't tell you the details.
詳しい事は私から言うわけにはいかないの
By the way, are you thirsty?
そうだ　喉渇いたでしょう
I'll get you something to drink.
ジュース買ってきましょうか
Damn it, they're treating us like kids!
くそ　まるで子供扱いだ
Why did they tell us to take our clothes and leave home in a hurry?
着替えを持って急いで家を出ろだなんて
本当なんだろうね
Mommy... Triple-H is a big hit!
御母さん　トリプルエッチ大ヒットだよ
I know!
分かった
I saw it on the news before, they evacuated the civilians
不発弾が地中から見つかって住民を避難させたって
after an unexploded bomb was discovered underground.
ニュースで見たことあるよ
There's probably one...
きっと家のしたからも
冠葉
Kanba?
Hello?
もしもし
おじさん　今　何処にいんの
Uncle!
Where are you now?
そっちにテレビあるだろ
Do you have a TV there?
速くつけろ
Turn it on now.
へー　なんだよ
Huh? Why?
They told us not to use the TV or phone.
テレビも電話も使うなって言われてんだけど
いいから　つけろ
十三年前の事件に　新たな展開がもたれされました
There has been a new development in the incident from 13 years ago.
Just turn it on.
It's on every channel. Hurry.
どこのチャンネルでもやってるから　速く
事件において 主導的役割を…
Suspected senior members of the group were reportedly residing in Tokyo.
まさか家の下から爆弾でも見つかった
される容疑者とも…市内に潜伏しているとの情報も
It's not an unexploded bomb, is it?
冠葉　これ
現在容疑者宅に警察の家宅捜査が入っているとのことです
Kanba, this is...
The police are currently conducting a search of the suspects' home.
Tokyo - Suginam
現場の中村記者と中継が繋がっております
We're going live to our reporter, Nakamura, at the scene.
Nakamura? Nakamura?
中村さん　中村さん
Isn't that our home?
これ 家だよね
Yes, I'm outside the suspects' home.
What is he saying?
この人何言ってんの
はい　こちら都内の容疑者の自宅前です
A large number of investigators just entered the house.
何だよ　これ　どういうことだよ
先ほど …サインが多数…見られました
What's this?
What's happening?
今　お前達の家にいる
I'm in your house right now.
I cannot hear anything from the house.
警察の捜査に立ち会ってるんだ
I'm aiding the police with their investigation.
It appears the investigation is quietly under way.
明け方まで続くそうだ
Looks like it's going to last all night.
It's usually a quiet neighborhood,
終わったら　そっちに行くから
I'll head over there when it's over.
それまで　ひまりを頼んだぞ
but tension is mounting among the residents.
Take care of Himari until then.
ちょ　おじさん　これってどういうこと
Hold on, Uncle.
What's going on?
I will continue to report as the story develops.
だよ　説明ぐらいしろよ
What the hell! At least explain!
Back to the studio.
冠葉　これ
Kanba... look...
Tokyo - Suginam
Takakura Kenzan
Takakura Chiemi
Suspect
繰り返します　現在主犯格と目される容疑者夫婦宅で警察の家宅捜査が行われております
Once again, the police are searching the home of the primary suspects.
Suspect
Time to wake up, Princess.
さあ　御姫様のお目覚めだ
Himari!
ひまり
お見事
Well done!
That was electrifying!
痺れました　眞悧先生
You're amazing, Dr. Satenetoshi!
I know, right?
だよね
Surprisingly, the Goddess changed her mind about death penalty for the youngest lamb.
不意に女神様は末の小羊に死の罰を与えるのをやめました
However, the Goddess did not revoke the punishment out of pity for the lambs,
しかし　女神様は小羊達を哀れんで罰を取りやめたわけでも
メリーさんに情けをかけた訳でもありません
nor was it out of mercy for Mary.
The Goddess said...
女神様は言いました
It would be no fun if the punishment ended here.
だって　これで罰が終わりじゃ　つまらないでしょ
Exactly!
その通り
What do you think of the word "fate"?
君は運命って言葉をどう思う
Does the concept of fate exist in reality?
運命は実在する概念だと思う
To put it simply, are people's future set in stone when they are born,
つまり　人の将来が生まれた時から予め決められていて
never to be challenged?
決して それに抗うことは出来ない
Do you believe in such a rule?
そういうルールがあるってことを信じる
Will you listen to my story for a while?
僕の話をちょっとだけ聞いてくれる
In the past...
昔ね
Hmm... I guess it was about 16 years ago.
うん　そう　十六年くらい前の話だけど
You see, there was this girl and she just appeared out of the blue.
その女の子はね
突然僕の前に現れたんだ
To my surprise, she was the same kind of person as me.
驚いたことに　彼女はね
僕と同じ種類の人間だったよ
And she had the same kind of eyes.
僕と同じ瞳
出会った瞬間
At first sight, I realized I wasn't a solitary existence in this world.
僕はこの世界で一人ぼっちじゃなかったことを知ったよ
嬉しかったな
I was so happy.
そうなんだよ 彼女に出会うまで
That's right.
Until I met her, I was all alone in this world.
僕はこの世界に一人だったからね
I had not a soul with whom to share the scenery before my eyes.
僕に見える風景は僕以外の誰にも見えない
And not a soul with whom to share the music in my ears.
僕が聞こえる音は僕以外の誰にも聞こえない
But... I heard the voices all over the world.
でも　世界中の人の声が聞こえていたんだ
I could hear the whole world crying out, "save me."
世界中の助けてって声が聞こえていたんだ
It's true.
ホントだよ
Thus, I could see the optimal path for the world.
だから　世界の進むべき方向も僕には見えていたんだ
嘘じゃないって
Seriously.
But, it saddened me.
でも　だから　悲しかったよ
Because the moment I saw her, I knew we were never meant to be.
だって　彼女と出会った瞬間
僕達は絶対に交わらないって　分かったから
Yes. She refused to side with me.
彼女は僕の味方になってくれなかった
彼女は僕を否定したんだ
She rejected me.
She rejected me, the only person who could see the same scenery.
同じ風景が見える唯一の存在である　僕を否定した
What is it? A question for me?
何　僕に質問
どうぞ
Do go ahead.
えっ　先の事
Oh?
About what just happened?
何故高倉ひまりの命を救ったのか
Why I saved Himari Takakura's life?
なぜだろうね
Why indeed.
まだ秘密だよ
It's still a secret.
You'll find out.
おいおいね
何だよ　怒るなよ
Lol wut? U mad?
じゃ　こう答えようか
Then, how's this for an answer?
僕はね　運命っていう概念が人の世界に存在するのか
I want to find out whether the concept of fate exists in the world...
そのルールが人の将来を支配しているかどうか
and whether or not that rule governs the universe.
それを確認したいんだ
I want you to witness it as well.
君にも それを確認して欲しいんだ　僕と一緒に
With me.
That's right, you two search for the Penguin Drum together.
そう　二人でピングドラムを探そうさ
Find out if it really exists.
そいつが本当に存在するかどうか
What do you say? It's not a bad deal, is it?
どう　悪い話じゃないだろう
Super Frog Saves
the
Penguin Drum
じゃ　引き続き 彼女のそばにいてあげてくれ
Well then, return by her side.
そして　君は僕と同じ風景を見るんだ
Eventually, you will see what I see.
あの兄弟と妹の行く末を一緒に確認しよう
Let us observe what will become of the siblings.
Farewell, my love.
じゃあね　僕の恋人
My love, the only one who can see the same scenery as I.
世界でたった一人の　僕と同じ風景を見ることができる　僕の恋人
See you again, in that world.
また　あの世界で再会しよう
She's stuck in bed again for a while, huh?
また暫く入院か
Monthly
Black
Kitty
Monthly
Black
Kitty
Hamana
Lake
But we were lucky to have such a nice doctor looking after her.
でも　運が良かったよ　あんないい先生に見てもらえることになって
Kanba?
冠葉
Huh?
Oh! You're right!
あー　そうだな
とにかく 俺達もひまりのために出来る事をしないとな
For now, we'll have to do whatever we can for Himari.
The symbol of the modern Tokyo, the new city's transportation network, the Tokyo Sky Metro.
新生東京のシンボル
新しい都市の交通網として誕生した東京スカイメトロ
Also known as TSM, marks its 10th anniversary of operation today.
TSM Operational for 10 Years
通称TSMも　本日開業十周年記念の年を迎えました
However, there is something we must never forget.
ですが　私達には決して 忘れてはならない事があります
失われた物が戻って来た
What we have lost may or may not have been restored.
Rome
Built
あるいは　元に戻ったわけではないのです
Rome
Built
曾てのシステムのような利便性への系統は許されないのです
Systematic advancement toward convenience must not continue.
そこに　人の心を反映させることが不可欠なのです
Our actions must reflect our humanity.
We must never again repeat such a tragedy.
私達はもう二度とあのような悲劇を繰り返してはならないのです
We'd like to hear from our viewers.
さて　ここで番組をご覧の皆様の声をお伺いしたいと思います
Built
Rome
Days
Please call the number on your screen.
お電話はご覧の番号へおかけください
Days
10 Year Anniversary
Make sure you call the right number.
お間違えないように
Yes?
はい
明るい場所と黒い場所は共存しなくてはならないの
Brightness and darkness must coexist.
全てを明るい光で照らしてしまうと
When you shine a bright light on everything,
darkness will strike the brightness in reaction, without fail.
必ず　その反動で暗い場所が明るい場所を攻撃するのよ
Um... what are you...
あのー　何を
Oh, no. It must be crushed soon.
嫌だわ　速くすり潰さないと
What?
ええ もしもし
Hello?
もしも
Hell-
あなたね
Oh, it's you.
ええ　万里夫はおかげさまで
Yes, Mario is doing fine.
I should express my gratitude.
一応お礼を申し上げておかなくてはね
That is not necessary.
礼には及ばないよ
You have paid a sufficient price.
君はそれに似合う十分な代価を払ったのだから
すり潰してやりたい
I want to crush it.
だよね
I know, right?
ところで　朗報だ
By the way, I have some information for you.
I know who has the other half of the diary.
行方不明になっていた日記の片割れ
その持ち主が分かったよ
誰　誰がもう半分を持ているの
Who? Who has the other half?
多蕗さん
Tabuki.
うん
Yes?
多蕗さんは高倉君達の事 あの兄弟の両親の事　知ってたんですね
Did you know about Takakura... the sibling's parents?
What?
えっ　そっか　高倉から聞いたのか
Oh, you must have heard from him.
Yes.
はい
彼らが自分の学校の生徒だって知った時
I was shocked too, when I found out they were students in my own school.
僕も驚いたよ
Isn't it a strange coincidence?
奇妙な偶然だろ
僕は被害者の友人　彼らは加害者の子供
I'm a friend of a victim.
They are the culprits' children.
事件の事　今でも覚えてますか
Do you still remember the incident?
正直に言うとね　あまり実感がないんだ
Honestly, I still can't believe it happened.
君のお姉さんとは事件の前日 学校の帰りに別れて　それっきりだからね
The last I saw of your sister was when we parted ways after school.
What would you do... if you found the culprits?
もし　犯人を見つけたらどうします
Well... their parents...
その　晶馬君達の両親を見つけたら
Who knows...
さあー
犯人って言われても
It's not like they killed her with their own hands.
直接目の前で何かをした連中じゃないからね
復讐したいとか そういう特別な感情はないんだ
I don't have any desire for vengeance or anything like that really.
あたしも実感がないんです
I can't really believe it either.
よく分からない
I don't really understand it.
でも　ママもパパもいっぱい悲しんだって聞きました
But I was told my parents were really saddened about it.
あたし　娘として失格かな
Does that make me a failure as a daughter?
いいんだよ　それで
There's nothing wrong with you.
あたし　姉に　桃果になりたかったな
I wished I could become my sister... become Momoka.
そうしたら　多蕗さんの悲しみも
Then I could've healed your pain and my parents' pain too.
ママやパパの悲しみも癒してあげられたのに
人生には　どうやっても取り戻せないことがある
There are things in life that cannot be restored.
でも 僕は君と出会えてよかったよ
But I'm glad to have met you.
君は
What about you?
Me too.
あたしもです
でも　だったら　晶馬君達のご両親の事は知らない方がよかったな
But I wish I'd never found out about their parents.
いや　きっと それを知ったことには意味があるんだよ
Suginami
Frog Park
No, I'm sure it happened for a reason.
どんな辛い事　悲しい事にも意味はある
There's a meaning no matter how sad and painful it may be.
無駄な事なんて　一つもないよ
Nothing in this world is pointless.
パパへ
Dear Daddy,
昨日は電話出来なくて　御免ね
I'm sorry I couldn't call you yesterday.
Can I come over to visit your new family next time?
今度はそっちの家に遊びに行ってもいいですか
とりあえず　ママには内緒で
I'll keep it a secret from Mom, for now.
Also, congratulations on your new marriage, Daddy.
あと　パパ　再婚おめでとう
Satoshi Oginome
Dear Daddy
I hope you will be happy together.
幸せになってね
Satoshi Oginome
Dear Daddy
I love the word "fate".
あたしは　運命って言葉が好き
ほら　だって　運命の出会いって言うでしょう
You know how they talk about "fated encounters"?
Built
Rome
Days
たった一つの出会いがその後の人生をすっかり変えてしまう
Just one single encounter can completely change your life.
Days
10 Year Anniversary
そんな特別な出会いは偶然じゃない
Such special encounters are not coincidences.
それはきっと　運命
They're definitely... fate.
勿論人生には幸せな出会いばかりじゃない
Of course, life is not all happy encounters.
Shoma - Three Years Ago - Shinjuku Kaioh Plaza Hotel -- Night - Takakura family's crime and punishment. Part 3: That day, everything was stripped from us.
There are many painful, sad predicaments.
嫌な事　悲しい事だって　沢山ある
It's hard to accept that misfortunes beyond your control are fate.
そういう不幸を運命だって受け入れるのはとても辛いこと
But I think...
でも　あたしはこう思う
there's a meaning no matter how sad and painful it may be.
悲しい事　辛い事にも　きっと意味はあるんだって
Nothing in this world is pointless.
Tokyo - Suginam
無駄な事なんて　一つもないよ
Takakura Kenzan
Takakura Chiemi
Suspect
だって　あたしは運命を信じているから
Because... I believe in fate.
嘘だ　父さんと母さんがあんなことするわけないだろ
You're lying!
There's no way my parents would do that!
Did you really do your research?
ちゃんと調べたのかよ
Unfortunately, it's true.
残念だけど　本当なの
警察では随分前からご両親の事を調べていて
The police have been investigating your parents for quite some time.
We have evidence of their roles in the incident, too.
犯行に関与した証拠も揃っているの
It's a lie!
嘘だ　俺達の父さんと母さんが
Our parents...
そんなー
would never...
ひまりに　なんて説明すればいいんだよ
How are we supposed to explain that to Himari?!
Kanba...
冠葉
It's all made up!
こんなの全部でっち上げだ
俺達の父さんと母さんは犯人じゃない
Our parents didn't do it.
They're not that kind of people!
そんな人間じゃない
僕と君の罪と罰
Crime and Punishment for You and Me
My feelings can't reach you
todokanai omoi
届かない思い
Our bonds being torn apart
hikisakareteku kizuna
引き裂かれてく絆
The clouds drift away regardlessly on a
nani mo nakatta you ni kumo wa nagarete iku sa
何もなかったように
雲は流れていくさ
haiiro no suiyoubi yo
Gray Wednesday
灰色の水曜日よ
Now, remember the spectacular past
saa omoidashite kagayaita koro wo
さあ　思い出して
輝いていた頃を
When everything was bright, when you fell in love
nani mo kamo mabushikute koi ni ochiteta koro wo
何もかもまぶしくて
恋に落ちてた頃を
Now, remember the time we loved each other
saa omoidashite aishiatteta koro wo
さあ　思い出して
愛し合ってた頃を
shinken na manazashi de mitsumeatteta koro wo
When we stared into each other's eyes
真剣な眼差しで
見つめ合ってた頃を
Now, remember the spectacular past
saa omoidashite kagayaiteta koro wo
さあ　思い出して
輝いていた頃を
When you lived for a dream
yume ni ikiteta koro wo
夢に生きてた頃を
When you loved each other
aishiatteta koro wo
愛し合ってた頃を
They're all lies!
皆嘘よ
Nothing in this world is true.
この世界にホントの事なんて一つもない
The only truth is the last word you will say to me tomorrow.
明日　あなたがあたしに言う最後の言葉だけがホントなんだ
Lily Hoshino
Survival Strategy. I love you!
生存戦略　大好きだよ